[
  {
    "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de 3(7+4^2)-47?",
    "choice1": "34",
    "choice2": "22",
    "choice3": "17",
    "choice4": "75",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de 3*4/2+10?",
    "choice1": "16",
    "choice2": "24",
    "choice3": "12",
    "choice4": "31",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de 15-(2^2)+4*5?",
    "choice1": "0",
    "choice2": "31",
    "choice3": "47",
    "choice4": "22",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de 44-3*6+1*1^2?",
    "choice1": "78",
    "choice2": "31",
    "choice3": "27",
    "choice4": "40",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de 133-63+2*2^2?",
    "choice1": "137",
    "choice2": "43",
    "choice3": "89",
    "choice4": "78",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de 20*4-15*6?",
    "choice1": "38",
    "choice2": "-10",
    "choice3": "2",
    "choice4": "14",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de 10-1*1-(1^2)?",
    "choice1": "8",
    "choice2": "13",
    "choice3": "4",
    "choice4": "-2",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de 4*3^1-40+13?",
    "choice1": "90",
    "choice2": "24",
    "choice3": "8",
    "choice4": "-15",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de 7*6+30/3?",
    "choice1": "89",
    "choice2": "12",
    "choice3": "52",
    "choice4": "42",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de 2^3+20-50?",
    "choice1": "-35",
    "choice2": "13",
    "choice3": "21",
    "choice4": "-22",
    "answer": 4
  }
]
